

CONTACT

Address: 49 Vaughn Way, Flat 67, Kimberley House Leicester Leicestershire LE14SG

Phone: 07585257716

Email: demontfortbg1998@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Verbal communication
- Foodservice
- Problem-solving
- Organisational ability
- Foodservice standard
- Superior communication skills

Bruno Goncalves

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a motivated person,

I recently moved to Leicester to finish my University there, I am currently studying and working at the same time as I always did since I was 17 years old. My dream is to find a job in Media production are, either working as a web designer or an audio related job.

WORK HISTORY

Bartender

10/2019 to Current

Tamatanga - Leicester, Leicestershire

- Started as a barback;
- I am slowly learning bartender techniques, and I work as a bartender more and more often;
- . Improved my costumer service;

Cooker

05/2019 to 09/2020

Creams - Leicester, LeicesterShire

- Started as a waiter;
- Moved to the Kitchen and learned how to use the informatics system to take orders:
- . Worked a lot as a pot washer as well;

Cooker

09/2018 to 04/2019

Grizzlers - Leicester, Leicestershire

- Started in the preparatory zone;
- . Learned how to work in a grill;
- Finally I worked answering the phone in order to note take away orders;
- . Worked in the packaging area;

Gas Station Operator

11/2016 to 09/2018

PetroMondego - Guarda, Portugal

- . Worked directly with costumers every day;
- Managed the store all by myself during my shifts;
- Performed the most various task, from the service for the client to the maintenance of the gas station.
- . Kept record of the money and handle it perfectly.

Factory Worker

06/2016 to 09/2016

DURA Automotive - Guarda, Portugal

- . Worked in a fast and paced environment;
- Performed control tests of the material produced every day;
- Learned how to work in a team;

EDUCATION

Escola Carolina Beatriz Angelo - Guarda

Economics

Escola Secundaria da Se - Guarda

Media and Communication **EnsiGuarda** - Guarda

Media Production, 2022

De Montfort University - Leicester